HEY! WE ARE
SO IN LUCK.
TREEGER SAID
WE COULD HAVE
ALL THIS COOL STUFF
FROM THE BASEMENT.
WAIT RIGHT THERE.
OH, NO, NO.
I'M PADDLING AWAY.
HUH?
WOW. REALLY?
WE GOT ALL THIS RUSTY CRAP
FOR FREE?
UH-HUH.
THIS AND A BUNCH
OF BUBBLE WRAP
AND SOME OF IT
IS NOT EVEN POPPED.
( quacking )
COULD WE BE
MORE WHITE TRASH?
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN YOUR DAY ♪
♪ YOUR WEEK, YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN
STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
HOW DESPERATE AM I?
OH, GOOD THING CHANDLER'S
NOT HERE.
HE ALWAYS WINS
AT THIS GAME.
I JUST TOLD MY MOM
I'D CATER A PARTY FOR HER.
HOW COME?
BECAUSE I NEED THE MONEY
AND I THOUGHT
IT'D BE A GREAT WAY
TO GET RID
OF THAT LAST LITTLE SMIDGEN
OF SELF-RESPECT.
I THINK THIS IS A GOOD THING.
I DON'T THINK MOM
WOULD HAVE HAVE HIRED YOU
IF SHE DIDN'T THINK YOU WERE
GOOD AT WHAT YOU DO.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO STICK UP FOR HER--
SHE CAN'T HEAR YOU.
HEY...
YOU GUYS HAVE ANY JUICE?
JUST PICKLE.
HEY, RACH, FUNNY STORY.
I BUMPED INTO JOANNA
ON THE STREET YESTERDAY.
MY BOSS, JOANNA?
WOW, THAT MUST HAVE
BEEN AWKWARD.
WELL, NO. SHE ASKED ME
IF I WANTED TO GET A DRINK.
( nervous laugh )
YOU, UH, DIDN'T SAY YES
TO THAT, DID YOU?
NO.
HELLO, RACHEL.
WELL, NOT AT FIRST.
WHAT IS SHE DOING HERE?
( makes bed creaking noises )
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
LAST TIME YOU WENT OUT WITH HER
YOU SAID SHE WAS
A BIG, DULL DUD.
I JUDGED HER TOO QUICKLY.
THIS TIME WE WERE ABLE
TO TAKE THE RELATIONSHIP
TO THE NEXT LEVEL.
( makes bed creaking noises )
WELL, LAST TIME,
I ALMOST GOT FIRED.
YOU MUST END IT.
YOU MUST END IT NOW.
IT'S NOT LIKE THIS IS
AN EVERYDAY OCCURRENCE FOR ME.
USUALLY, I'M PRETTY MUCH
IN THERE BY MYSELF.
( makes bed creaking noises )
CHANDLER!
PROMISE ME
YOU WILL END IT.
OKAY. I PROMISE.
I'LL END IT.
THANK YOU.
I HOPE YOU KNOW
WHAT I'M GIVING UP FOR YOU
BECAUSE SHE'S NOT JUST
THE BOSS IN YOUR OFFICE...
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
( chuckling ):
YEAH.
OH, SORRY.
I KNEW WHAT HE MEANT.
HOW'S THE
HIRED HELP?
DOING GREAT.
QUICHES ARE
COMING ALONG.
WHAT'S THIS?
BLUE NAIL POLISH?
YEAH. I THOUGHT
IT WAS CUTE.
HA! THAT'S WHAT
YOUR GRANDMOTHER'S
HANDS LOOKED LIKE
WHEN WE FOUND HER.
LET ME ASK YOU A QUESTION.
WHY DID YOU HIRE ME?
OH, WELL, RICHARD RAVED
ABOUT THE FOOD
AT HIS PARTY.
OF COURSE, YOU WERE
SLEEPING WITH HIM.
THEN I HEARD THE FOOD
AT THAT LESBIAN WEDDING
WAS VERY NICE.
I ASSUME YOU
WEREN'T SLEEPING
WITH ANYONE THERE--
THOUGH, AT LEAST
THAT WOULD BE SOMETHING.
OH, MY GOD!
DID YOU HEAR THAT?
SHE HIRED ME BECAUSE
SHE THINKS I'M GOOD.
OKAY. I DIDN'T HEAR THAT.
OH, YEAH. SHE DIDN'T
HIRE ME OUT OF PITY.
IT WASN'T SO SHE
COULD PICK ON ME
IN FRONT OF HER FRIENDS.
SHE ACTUALLY
THINKS I'M GOOD.
WOW!
AND, HEY, IT'S COOL
IF YOU'RE A LESBIAN.
( knock at door )
GOOD AFTERNOON.
ARE YOU THE
DECISION-MAKER
OF THE HOUSE?
UH...
DO YOU CURRENTLY OWN
A SET OF ENCYCLOPEDIAS?
NO, NO, BUT TRY THE CLASSIFIEDS.
PEOPLE SELL EVERYTHING IN THERE.
ACTUALLY,
I'M NOT BUYING.
I'M SELLING.
LET ME ASK YOU
ONE QUESTION.
DO YOUR FRIENDS EVER
HAVE A CONVERSATION
AND YOU JUST NOD ALONG
EVEN THOUGH YOU'RE
NOT REALLY SURE
WHAT THEY'RE
TALKING ABOUT?
I'M TELLING YOU,
IT'S TOTALLY UNCONSTITUTIONAL.
I TOTALLY AGREE.
YEAH.
I THINK HE DESERVES
A NOBEL PRIZE.
NO!
HOW CAN YOU
SAY THAT?
I MEAN, IT WAS LIKE
THE ALGONQUIN KID'S TABLE.
( all laughing )
( nervous chuckle )
EXCUSE ME.
I'M SORRY.
YOU HAVEN'T
SAID ANYTHING
FOR ABOUT
2 1/2 MINUTES.
ARE YOU AT ALL
INTERESTED?
YEAH, YEAH. YEAH, OH, YEAH.
COME ON IN.
OKAY.
THAT'S WEIRD.
WHAT?
YOUR NAILS.
I NEVER WEAR FAKE ONES.
I JUST DID IT SO MY MOM
WOULDN'T GIVE ME GRIEF
ABOUT BITING THEM.
OH. NO, I MEANT
IT'S WEIRD
THAT YOU ONLY
HAVE NINE NOW.
OH, MY GOD.
WAIT A MINUTE.
I HAD THEM WHEN I PUT...
OH, MY GOD,
IT'S IN THE QUICHE!
OH, MY GOD!
OKAY, DON'T PANIC.
I'M GOING TO GET YOU
ANOTHER SET OF NAILS.
NO ONE'S GOING TO KNOW,
AND YOU'RE GOING TO LOOK GREAT.
OH. OH, IT'S 'CAUSE
THEY'RE GOING TO EAT.
THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
HONEY, DON'T BITE
YOUR NAILS.
OKAY, UH, PLEASE DON'T
FREAK OUT, UM, BUT, UH...
THERE'S A BLUE FINGERNAIL
IN-IN ONE OF THE QUICHE CUPS
AND THERE'S NO WAY
TO KNOW WHICH ONE.
AND WHOEVER FINDS IT
WINS THE PRIZE.
I'M NOT FREAKING OUT.
WHY ARE YOU LAUGHING?
IT'S JUST THAT NOW
YOUR FATHER OWES ME $5.
WHAT? YOU BET
I'D LOSE A NAIL?
OH, NO. DON'T BE SILLY.
I JUST BET THAT
I'D NEED THESE.
FROZEN LASAGNAS?
YOU BET THAT I'D SCREW UP?
SO ALL THAT STUFF
ABOUT HIRING ME
BECAUSE I WAS GOOD WAS...
NO. THAT WAS ALL TRUE.
THIS WAS JUST IN CASE
YOU PULLED A MONICA.
YOU PROMISED DR. WEINBERG
YOU'D NEVER USE THAT PHRASE.
OH, HONEY, COME ON.
HAVE A SENSE OF HUMOR.
YOU'RE NEVER ABLE
TO LAUGH AT YOURSELF.
THAT'S RIGHT.
( chuckles )
MY MOM DOESN'T HAVE
ANY FAITH IN ME.
THAT'S HILARIOUS!
( forced laugh )
I DON'T GET IT.
NO, I HAVE FAITH.
NO, YOU HAVE LASAGNAS.
( bell rings )
OH, THE RUINED QUICHES
ARE READY.
IT JUST DOESN'T FEEL
LIKE WE'RE BREAKING UP.
NO, WE ARE.
I'M SAD.
OKAY.
( phone rings )
YES?
CAN YOU WAIT
TILL TOMORROW?
ALL RIGHT.
UNBELIEVABLE!
THANKS.
NO. THAT WAS MY BOSS.
I HAVE TO GO.
OKAY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M GETTING DRESSED.
WHY?
WHEN I WALK OUTSIDE NAKED
PEOPLE THROW GARBAGE AT ME.
WAIT.
I WANT TO SHOW YOU SOMETHING.
WHAT IS IT?
JUST A LITTLE GAG GIFT
SOMEBODY GAVE ME.
PUT YOUR HANDS
TOGETHER.
( chuckles )
YOU'RE NOT THE BOSS OF ME.
YEAH, YOU ARE.
HMM...
SAUCY.
I'LL BE BACK
IN TWO MINUTES.
YOU'RE, UH... YOU'RE GOING
TO LEAVE ME LIKE THIS?
KNOWING YOU'RE HERE,
WAITING FOR ME
I THINK THAT'S KIND OF EXCITING,
DON'T YOU?
OKAY, BUT IF YOU DON'T
COME BACK SOON...
THERE'S PRETTY MUCH NOTHING
I CAN DO ABOUT IT.
OH, HI.
HI. I BROUGHT YOU BACK
A MACAROON.
GREAT. I'LL KEEP IT IN MY BUTT
WITH YOUR NOSE.
THAT'S WEIRD.
SHE LOCKED THE DOOR.
YOU KNOW WHY?
SHE'S GOT THE CHRISTMAS
BONUS LIST IN THERE.
I SAW HER WORKING ON IT
THIS MORNING.
OKAY. SWEAR YOU WON'T TELL,
BUT WHEN MARK LEFT
HE GAVE ME A KEY
TO JOANNA'S OFFICE.
YOU WANT TO SEE THE LIST?
YEAH!
( both gasp )
HI.
HOW ARE YOU?
( phone ringing )
( ringing continues )
HELLO. JOANNA...
...'S OFFICE.
Joanna:
It's me. I'm really,
really sorry
but I may be
a little while longer.
HOW LITTLE?
A couple of hours.
I feel awful.
THIS ISN'T FUNNY.
GET BACK HERE RIGHT NOW.
I can't.
WHY NOT?
I'm in my boss's car.
WHAT?!
Uh-oh. Tunnel.
( intercom buzzes )
( buzzing )
WHAT?
Chandler:
Rachel, could I see you
for a moment?
OKAY, HERE'S THE SITUATION--
THE KEYS TO THE CUFFS
ARE ON THE BACK OF THE DOOR.
COULD YOU BE A DOLL
AND GRAB THEM
AND SCOOT ON OVER HERE
AND UNLOCK ME?
AND, ON A TOTALLY
SEPARATE SUBJECT
THAT IS A LOVELY PANTSUIT.
YOU PROMISED
YOU WOULD BREAK UP WITH HER.
I DID BREAK UP WITH HER.
SHE JUST TOOK IT
REALLY, REALLY WELL.
AND THE FACT THAT YOU WERE
JEOPARDIZING MY CAREER
NEVER ENTERED YOUR MIND?
IT DID ENTER MY MIND
BUT THEN SOMETHING
HAPPENED THAT MADE IT
SHOOT RIGHT OUT.
YOU KNOW WHAT, CHANDLER?
YOU GOT YOURSELF
INTO THOSE CUFFS
YOU GET YOURSELF OUT OF THEM.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
I CAN'T GET MYSELF
RIGHT OUT OF THEM.
YOU MUST HAVE ME CONFUSED
WITH THE
AMAZING CHANDLER.
COME ON! YOU HAVE TO UNLOCK ME.
SHE COULD BE GONE FOR HOURS
AND I'M COLD AND...
OH, CHANDLER!
ALL RIGHT. THIS IS IT.
YOU NEVER SEE JOANNA AGAIN.
NEVER.
YOU NEVER COME
INTO THIS OFFICE AGAIN.
FINE.
YOU GIVE ME BACK MY WALKMAN.
I...
I NEVER BORROWED YOUR WALKMAN.
WELL, THEN I LOST IT.
YOU BUY ME ONE.
YOU GOT IT.
HERE WE GO.
COME ON.
THIS IS GREAT.
AH...!
DOES IT HURT?
NO. I JUST ALWAYS
SEE GUYS DOING THIS
WHEN THEY GET HANDCUFFS
TAKEN OFF THEM.
HELLO, SWEET PANTS.
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO TELL JOANNA?
ABOUT WHAT?
WHEN SHE SEES YOU'RE GONE,
SHE'LL KNOW I LET YOU OUT
AND I WAS IN HERE
AND I'LL GET FIRED.
I'LL MAKE SOMETHING UP.
I'M GOOD AT LYING.
I ACTUALLY DID
BORROW YOUR WALKMAN.
THERE'S NOTHING
TO MAKE UP.
SHE'S GOING TO KNOW I HAVE
A KEY TO HER OFFICE.
I'VE GOT TO GET YOU LOCKED
BACK THE WAY YOU WERE.
OH, I DON'T THINK SO.
NAH, NAH, NAH,
NAH, NO...
NO, NO, NO!
NO!
( shrieks )
WELL, THIS IS
MUCH BETTER.
SO, HERE'S SOMEBODY
INTERESTING, JOEY.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT VAN GOGH?
UH... HE CUT OFF HIS EAR.
AND?
I'M OUT.
HE PAINTED THAT.
WOW, THAT'S PRETTY NICE.
I THOUGHT HE CUT OFF
HIS EAR 'CAUSE HE SUCKED.
WHAT ELSE
YOU GOT IN THERE?
LET'S SEE. UH...
WHERE DOES
THE POPE LIVE?
IN THE WOODS.
NO, WAIT. WAIT.
THAT'S THE JOKE ANSWER.
ACTUALLY,
IT'S VATICAN CITY.
NOW, UH...
WHAT DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT VULCANIZED RUBBER?
SPOCK'S BIRTH CONTROL.
YOU NEED THESE BOOKS.
( knock at door )
HEY.
HI.
THIS USED
TO BE YOUR ROOM?
WOW, YOU MUST
HAVE BEEN
IN REALLY GOOD
SHAPE AS A KID.
OH, I'M SUCH AN IDIOT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I ACTUALLY
THOUGHT SHE COULD CHANGE.
LOOK, WHO CARES WHAT
YOUR MOM THINKS?
SO YOU PULLED
A MONICA.
OH, GOOD.
I'M GLAD THAT'S CATCHING ON.
WHY DOES THAT HAVE
TO BE A BAD THING?
JUST CHANGE WHAT IT MEANS.
GO DOWN THERE
AND PROVE YOUR MOTHER WRONG.
YOU FINISH THE JOB
YOU WERE HIRED TO DO.
WE'LL CALL THAT
"PULLING A MONICA."
WHAT?
OKAY, UM... IF A KID
GETS STRAIGHT A's
HIS PARENTS WOULD SAY,
"YEAH! YOU PULLED A MONICA."
OR A FIREMAN SAVES A BABY,
AND THEY GO, "YEAH, I KNOW.
HE PULLED
A MONICA."
OR SOMEONE HITS A HOME RUN
AND THE ANNOUNCER SAYS,
"YEAH, THAT ONE'S OUT OF HERE."
'CAUSE SOME THINGS DON'T CHANGE.
ALL RIGHT. I'LL GO DOWN THERE
BUT I'M NOT GOING
TO SERVE THE LASAGNA.
I'M GOING TO SERVE
SOMETHING THAT I MAKE.
WAIT.
OOH.
OH, WOW!
OH, MY BREASTS
ARE REALLY STRONG.
( grunting )
OH, CHANDLER...
CHANDLER, PLEASE.
I HAVE TO GET YOU LOCKED UP
BACK THE WAY YOU WERE.
I AM SO GOING TO LOSE MY JOB.
SHE'S VERY PRIVATE
ABOUT HER OFFICE.
NOW I KNOW WHY.
LOOK, YOU WERE
IN TROUBLE EITHER WAY.
IF SHE SEES ME LOCKED TO THIS
INSTEAD OF THE CHAIR
SHE'LL KNOW YOU WERE IN HERE.
SO YOU MIGHT AS WELL
JUST LET ME GO.
WHAT IF I CLEAN YOUR BATHROOM
FOR A MONTH?
IT STILL
WOULDN'T BE CLEAN.
ALL I WANT IS MY FREEDOM.
FOOT RUBS FOR A MONTH.
FREEDOM!
I'LL TAKE ALL OF YOUR PHOTOS
AND I'LL PUT THEM INTO ALBUMS.
FREEDOM! I WANT MY FREEDOM!
WHY WON'T
YOU HEAR ME?
SOPHIE,
HELP ME!
SOPHIE, SIT!
FREEDOM!
( muffled yelling )
WILL YOU
JUST CALM DOWN?
( muffled
yelling )
I'M GOING TO SAY THIS
FOR THE LAST TIME.
WOULD YOU PLEASE JUST...?
WELL, THERE'S A LOT
I DIDN'T KNOW ABOUT VOMIT.
( quacking )
IN A MINUTE.
SO, WHAT DO YOU SAY, JOEY?
YOU GET THE WHOLE SET
OF ENCYCLOPEDIAS FOR $1,200.
THAT WORKS OUT
TO JUST 50 BUCKS A BOOK.
$1,200?
YOU THINK I HAVE $1,200?
I'M HOME IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE DAY
AND I GOT PATIO FURNITURE
IN MY LIVING ROOM.
I GUESS
THERE'S A FEW THINGS
YOU DON'T GET
FROM BOOK LEARNING.
WELL, UH... WHAT CAN YOU SWING?
HOW ABOUT ZERO DOWN
AND ZERO A MONTH
FOR A LONG, LONG TIME?
YOU DON'T HAVE... ANYTHING?
YOU WANT
TO SEE WHAT I GOT?
OKAY. I GOT...
A BABY TOOTSIE ROLL
A MOVIE STUB,
KEYS, A KLEENEX...
A ROCK...
AND AN ARMY MAN. MAN!
OKAY, I...
I GET THE PICTURE.
UH... THANKS
FOR YOUR TIME.
AND A 50.
HUH.
THESE MUST BE CHANDLER'S PANTS.
FOR 50 BUCKS,
YOU CAN GET ONE BOOK.
WHAT WILL IT BE--
"A," "B," "C"?
I THINK I'M GOING
TO STICK WITH THE "V."
I WANT TO SEE
HOW THIS BAD BOY TURNS OUT.
Rachel:
I, UH...
WILL BUY AND WRAP
ALL OF YOUR CHRISTMAS GIFTS.
NO!
I, UH... I'LL SQUEEZE YOU FRESH
ORANGE JUICE EVERY MORNING.
WITH EXTRA PULP?
YEAH!
NO!
( grunts )
I'VE GOT IT.
YOU DON'T HAVE IT.
I HAVE SO GOT IT.
THERE'S GOING
TO BE RUMORS ABOUT THIS.
THERE'S NO WAY TO STOP IT.
SOPHIE KNOWS.
MONICA AND PHOEBE KNOW.
HOW COME MONICA
AND PHOEBE KNOW?
OH, I CALLED THEM.
AND WHEN THEY ASK ME WHAT I SAW
I CAN BE VERY GENEROUS...
OR VERY STINGY.
GO ON.
I CAN MAKE YOU A LEGEND.
I CAN MAKE YOU
THIS GENERATION'S MILTON BERLE.
AND MILTON BERLE HAS...?
AW, NOT COMPARED TO YOU.
WELL, THEY'RE NOT EVEN
TOUCHING THE LASAGNA.
REALLY?
THEY LOVE
YOUR CASSEROLE.
YES!
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE
JUST A LITTLE WHILE AGO
THIS WAS NOTHING
BUT INGREDIENTS.
EVERYONE SEEMS
TO LIKE YOUR DISH.
AND YOU?
I THOUGHT IT WAS...
QUITE TASTY.
SO IF EVERYONE LIKED IT
AND YOU LIKED IT
THAT WOULD
MAKE THIS A SUCCESS.
WHICH WOULD MAKE YOU...
A BITCH?
WELL, I WAS GOING
FOR "WRONG"
BUT WE CAN USE YOUR WORD.
YES, WELL, I WAS WRONG
AND I HAVE TO SAY...
YOU REALLY
IMPRESSED ME TODAY.
WOW.
YOU MIGHT EVEN SAY
THAT SHE PULLED A MONICA.
SHE DOESN'T KNOW
WE SWITCHED IT.
AND THE NEXT TIME
YOU CATER FOR ME
THERE'LL BE NOTHING
BUT ICE IN THE FREEZER.
THAT REALLY
MEANS A LOT.
OY, MOM,
DON'T BITE YOUR NAILS.
HELLO.
HEY.
HELLO, CHANDLER.
I LOVE YOU.
HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
OH...
( whispering )
NO, HE DOESN'T.
( laughing )
TWO HOURS, THAT LASTED.
SO DID YOU BREAK UP
WITH JOANNA?
I THINK SO.
IT'S A GOOD THING YOU GOT OUT
WHEN YOU DID
BEFORE SHE BLEW UP
LIKE THAT VESUVIUS.
THE VOLCANO?
YEAH. AND SPEAKING OF VOLCANOES
MAN, ARE THEY A VIOLENT,
IGNEOUS ROCK FORMATION.
WHAT?
OH, YEAH-- LAVA SPEWING,
HOT ASH...
OF COURSE, SOME ARE DORMANT.
WHY ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT VOLCANOES
ALL OF A SUDDEN?
WE CAN TALK
ABOUT SOMETHING ELSE.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT?
VIVISECTION?
THE VAS...
DEFERENS?
THE VIETNAM WAR?
OH, DID ANYBODY
SEE THAT DOCUMENTARY
ON THE KOREAN WAR?
All:
OH, YEAH.
KOREA IS SUCH
A BEAUTIFUL COUNTRY.
WITH SUCH A SAD HISTORY.
YEAH.
COULD THERE BE MORE KIMS?
Joanna:
WHO'S OUT THERE?
IT'S ME. GOOD MORNING.
RACHEL, COULD YOU
COME IN HERE A MOMENT PLEASE?
SURE. THEY DIDN'T
HAVE POPPY-SEED BAGELS
SO I... OH, MY WORD!
HI. I SEEM TO HAVE HAD
A SLIGHT OFFICE MISHAP.
COULD YOU PLEASE
GET THE KEY
OFF THE BACK
OF THE DOOR FOR ME?
YEAH. OF COURSE. UM...
I'M SO SORRY.
YOU CAN TELL
YOUR FRIEND CHANDLER
THAT WE'RE DEFINITELY
BROKEN UP THIS TIME.